I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Ryusuke. I'm going to form
the ultimate band.
（栄二(えいじ)）竜介(りゅうすけ)…
俺は… 最強のバンドをつくる
So will I.
（竜介）俺も つくるよ
（コユキ）あっ え～と…
Umm...
I was hoping to borrow that
Dying Breed CD from their indie days.
ダイブリの
インディーズ時代のＣＤ—
借りに行こうと思って…
Koyuki. If you have time, follow me.
（竜介）コユキ
時間があるなら ついてきな
Ryusuke-kun, how's the guitar?
竜介君 ギターどう？
-Concentrate on the sound.
-Sound?
音に集中してみな
音？
Close your eyes and focus on the sound.
目をつぶって 音に集中するんだ
Can you hear the bass?
The level is different.
ベースの音が分かるか？
レベルが違う
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I'm about to go there.
Well, don't get pissed.
Okay, I'll be there.
Ryusuke-kun, is something wrong?
竜介君 どうかした？
Yeah, something came up.
ああ… ちょっとな
He was awfully mad.
あいつ かなり怒ってたなー
Didn't you hear me? I said no thanks.
（真帆(まほ)の英語）
I told you I'm just waiting for my brother,
not for fuckin' guys like you.
I'm not a whore like you think!
（真帆：英語）
〈私は あんた達が考えているような
軽い女じゃないぞ！〉
（外国人１：英語）〈いや
そんなこと言ってないじゃん〉
No, I didn't mean it! Sorry.
〈困ったなぁ〉
Bullshit, you fuckin' bastard! Go away!
（真帆）〈何 言ってんだよ
このダメダメヤロー！〉
Wow...You're too scary.
（外国人２：英語）
〈こ… 怖い女だ〉
Scary?! Who do you think makes me scary?
（真帆）ハ～イ！
Hey, what's going on? Who are they?
（竜介：英語）〈おい どーした？
こんなとこで何してんだよ？〉
Well, they were hitting on me.
They should go to hell.
（真帆）〈彼らが しつこく
ナンパしてくるから切れた〉
（竜介）〈ハハッ
あいつら超ビビってたぜ〉
They're both freaked out like shit.
'Cuz you're late!
〈もう！
兄貴が遅れるからじゃん！〉
Well, sorry about that.
〈いやぁ すまんすまん〉
Oh, yeah. Let me introduce you.
（竜介）お そうそう 紹介するよ
コユキは 真帆と同じ14歳だ
Koyuki is 14, same as you, Maho.
I know!
-And what'll you have?
-Whatever.
（竜介）で 何食べんの？
（真帆）もう 何でもいいよ
Okay, then. Koyuki, take care of it.
（竜介）そっか…
じゃ～ 頼んだぞ コユキ
I'm going to talk to Taira, the bassist.
ベース弾いてた
平(たいら)ってヤツと会ってくる
I've gotta catch him early,
or he'll be taken.
急がねえと 売れちまいそうなんだ
平のヤツがさ
The main thing in a band is...
a bassist and drummer.
バンドで中心になるのは
ベースとドラムなんだ
Is a beef bowl okay?
（コユキ）牛丼でいい？
Okay, see you later.
I called some friends from school.
You don't mind, do you?
学校の友達 呼んじゃったけど
いいよね
Sure.
Say, the other day, I met this guy,
and he tried to pick me up!
（リサ）ねえねえ この前さ～
ナンパされちゃって～
But he was such an asshole!
But he had a BMW convertible!
Really? That's cool! I love that car!
I know...But he was awfully creepy!
（リサ）そうなんだけど
彼 超気持ち悪いんだ～
His eyes twitched in this weird way
and it made me sick!
But Risa, you always
get stuck with weirdos.
I know...
Why don't you wait for Maho's rejects?
ノ～ 私なんか さっき
ティス 貧乏そうな外国人に…
Oh no. Some poor-looking foreigners
hit on me earlier.
-Poor foreigners? That sucks!
-Yeah...
（リサ）貧乏そうな外国人～？
There's never cool guys.
I like guys riding Porsches.
-Then I want a Ferrari.
-Me too!
Hey, let's go clubbing now.
We might find our dream guy.
Yay, let's go!
Yeah, I wanna go, but I'm broke.
（真帆）
でも私 お金ないから…
-Umm...I...
-Come on!
（コユキ）あの… 俺…
Fine, the dream guy will pay for you.
Yeah, free buy!
I have something to
take care of, so I'll be going.
用があるんで… 先に帰ります
They don't teach English properly
in Japan, is what I feel.
（コユキ）日本の英語教育は
間違ってる… と思う
Dutch, huh?
（平）ワリカンか…
お前 日本語うまくなったなぁ
Your Japanese has improved.
Is that meant to be a compliment?
それ 褒めてるんすか？
Eiji and I jammed the other day.
おととい 栄二とジャムったんだ
He's getting better, amazingly fast.
あいつ すげえ早さで
うまくなってるぞ
I finish school this year,
and I'm thinking seriously about my future.
俺も ことしで学校終わりだし
本気で将来考えてる
If you want to make music with me,
bring me a really great vocalist.
俺とやりたきゃ
すげえボーカルを連れてこい
A vocalist, huh?
（竜介）ボーカルか…
Yo!
（真帆）よう！
（コユキ）うわっ
W-what happened?
ど どうしたの？
I have no place to crash tonight.
So I'm going to Ryusuke's place.
（真帆）きょう帰るとこないの
だから竜介のとこ行くんだ
Umm, the other day...
あ この前…
（真帆）ん？
I'm sorry I laughed at you
about not knowing kanji.
漢字のことで笑ったりして
ごめんなさい
ハハハ… いいよ
だって私 漢字弱いし… さ
Don't worry about it.
Besides, I am bad at kanji.
I got fired from a diner yesterday
because I didn't know the language.
きのうも言葉のことで
弁当屋クビになっちゃったんだ
Are you serious?
そんな…
I was so mad, I yelled and cried
that I was going back to America.
（真帆）
もう すっごく頭にきて—
アメリカ帰る！ って
泣き叫んでたら…
Then my dad slapped me.
パパに ぶたれた
（コユキ）大丈夫？
Are you all right?
You're very kind, Koyuki.
コユキは優しいね
But you don't seem to like my friends.
でも 私の友達のことは嫌いみたい
B-because I left early?
（コユキ）な 何で？
先に帰ったから？
You didn't try to talk to them.
話しかけてこなかったから
-But the language...
-ls that it? The language?
（コユキ）だって言葉が…
（真帆）そうかな 言葉のせいかな
（コユキ）えっ…
Everyone says the same thing.
（真帆）みーんな 同じ答え
Well, let's go see Beck!
さ！ ベックに会いに行こう！
Huh? Beck?!
（コユキ）えっ… ベック？
Beck!
（真帆）ベック！
アハハッ フフフ…
（コユキ）うわ～っ！ わあっ
（コユキ）
ああ… うわぁ… うわ…
Hey, Beck! I haven't seen you
in a while, yet you ignore me!
（真帆）なんだよ ベック！
久しぶりなのに私は無視かよ～
助けて！ 真帆ちゃん
Please help me, Maho-chan!
Stop adding "-chan" to my name.
ちゃん付けは やめてくれない？
Hi, Beck...
（真帆）ハイ ベーック
How's it going?
Brother taking care of you?
Such a pretty full moon.
きれいなフルムーン
It's a full moon tonight.
（コユキ）きょうは満月なんだ
Full moon sways...
（真帆）♪「MOON ON THE WATER」
Gently in the night of one fine day...
Maho, you're amazing. You can
speak English and you sing great.
（コユキ）真帆はすごいよ
英語で話せるし 歌はうまいし—
And you're cute...
かわいいし…
I know you'll make it as a singer!
真帆なら絶対 歌手になれる
As if!
（真帆）まさか 私には
ボーカルの才能なんてないよ
I have no talent as a singer.
My dream is to study movies in New York.
私の夢は ニューヨークで
映画の勉強をすることなんだ
Full moon sways...
（コユキ）♪「MOON ON THE WATER」
Gently in the night of one fine day.
On my way...
Looking for a moment with my dear...
It's my favorite song by Dying Breed.
ダイブリの曲で一番好きな歌なんだ
Hey, Tanaka!
（泉(いずみ)）こら 田中！
（コユキ）う…
（泉）何か見つかった？
Find something?
（コユキ）あ～ 泉ちゃんか
驚かせないでよ～
Oh, it's you, Izumi-chan!
Don't scare me like that!
ハァ…
-So, are you willing?
-Huh?
（泉）で やる気はあるの？
（コユキ）えっ
Stop by the municipal pool at 6 pm.
（泉）きょうの６時
市民プールに行ってみな
Pool?
（コユキ）プール…
（泉）うん
Don't be late, now.
You'll find out when you get there.
遅れずに行けよな
行けば分かるさ
The municipal pool?
市民プール…
Well then, I'll see you later.
（男性）それじゃ… また
"Business envelopes, fabric tape,
aluminum foil, polyester bags"
Please consider the financing!
（斎藤(さいとう)）
ぜひとも 融資の件—
Please consider the financing!
よろしく
お願い申し上げます
（斎藤）何とぞ…
どうか ひとつ… よろしく！
Please! Thank you!
"Saito Paper Company"
フ～… ５時半か…
5:30 huh?
（斎藤）よいしょ！
There!
（斎藤）さーってと…
And now...
（コユキ）ブハァーッ
ハァ… ハァ… ハァ…
（監視員）
えー そこの少年
Hey, kid...
（監視員）コースロープに
つかまらないでくださーい
Please don't grab onto the lane ropes.
ハァ… そんなこと…
言ったって…
I know, but...
Hey, kid! If you're in the
50 meter pool, don't stop!
（監視員）えー そこの少年！
50メートルコースでは止まらないで
泳いでくださ～い
（女性１）キャーッ！
-There he is.
-Let's go home.
（女性２）出た出た
（女性３）あー 帰ろっと
あんたさ キックは
まあまあなんだけど—
Hey, your kick is okay,
but you pull with your elbow,
so you're not cutting into the water.
肘から先にプルしてるから
水をかき込めてないんだよ
（女性１）は？ はぁ…
Huh? Oh...
Okay! Hook your feet
against the pool and practice!
はいっ このままプルブイ
足につけて練習！
（女性１）あっ…
-Let's give it a try!
-W-who is he?
（斎藤）
さあ いってみようかー
（コユキ）な 何だ あの人…
（女性１）あ はい…
He's the famous man of this pool.
（監視員）彼は ここのプールの
名物おじさんさ
Famous?
名物…
His name's Saito-san, and he
was once an Olympic swimmer.
斎藤さんっていって
元五輪強化選手なんだけどさ～
泳ぎの下手な人 見つけると
教えずにはいられないっていうか…
So whenever he sees a poor swimmer,
he can't help but teach.
An Olympic swimmer?
オリンピック選手？
Well, he's not a bad guy.
ま 悪い人じゃないんだけどね～
（泉）あれ？ おかしいなー
Huh? That's strange...
（友人）泉～！
25メータープールにいたよ
Izumi!
He's in the 25-meter pool.
One, two, three, four...
（斎藤）いち にい さん しっ
ごー ろく しち… ハイッ！
おお 私の計算どおりね
Just as I figured!
Koyuki got caught!
コユキのヤツ
しっかり捕まっちゃいました
（斎藤）少年 準備はいいか!?
Kid, are you ready?
You're giving me a
15-meter handicap, right?
ハンデ 15メートルですよね
（斎藤）ああ 容赦なしの… んんっ
真剣勝負だぞ
Yeah...This is serious, a real contest.
はいっ で 僕が勝ったら…
Yes. And if I win?
約束どおり マンツーマンで
親切指導してやろう
As promised, I'll train you man to man.
はい…
（斎藤）で 君が負けたら…
All right.
-And if you lose...
-lf I lose?
負けたら…
（斎藤）君を… 殴る！
I'll hit you!
Huh?!
（斎藤）
う～… むろん手加減なしだ！
And I won't hold back!
何で そんなこと…
Why would you do that?!
Kid...In the grown-up world,
there are many painful things!
少年 大人の世界にはな—
つらいことが
いっぱいあるんだよ！
Now get set!
はい 位置について！
Ready!
よーい！
Go!
どん！
Five meters.
５メートル…
Ten meters.
10メートル…
Fifteen meters!
15メートル！
Victory is mine!
もらった！ あっ…
（斎藤）あれ？
ハァッ… ハァッ… やった…
I...did it!
（泉）斎藤さん！
Saito-san...
お久しぶりです
It's been a long time.
（コユキ）泉ちゃん！
Izumi-chan!
Oh!
おお！ 君は確か我が母校
伊原東(いはらひがし)中 水泳部の後輩
You're in the swim club at my alma mater,
Ihara East Middle School!
How is Suzuki-sensei's lumbago?
顧問の鈴木(すずき)先生の腰痛はどうだい？
（泉）おかげで だいぶ
よくなったみたいですが—
I think it's much better.
斎藤さん また臨時コーチに
来てください！
Saito-san, please come
and coach us again!
Oh, really? I'm glad that
someone like you appreciates me!
（斎藤）おー！ そうか
君みたいな子が望んでくれるなら…
（泉）
それじゃ コユキが声かけたの？
-Then you talked to him?
-Yeah.
（コユキ）うん
（泉）あんたって…
You're really...
I asked him for some advice. And then...
ちょっとアドバイスして
もらおうかなって そしたら…
そしたら？
And then?
We somehow wound up in a race.
いつの間にか
勝負することになってたんだ
（斎藤）コユキ君
（コユキ）えっ？
Koyuki-kun!
Want some?
これ食べない？
-N-no, thank you.
-No?
（コユキ）だ… 大丈夫です
そう… じゃ あしたもまた
元気に練習しましょっ
Well, let's practice again tomorrow!
Good night!
それじゃ
He's like a different person.
別人みたい…
Saito-san is a really warm-hearted
gentleman outside the pool.
（泉）斎藤さん プールの外じゃ
温厚な紳士なんだよ
He listens to U.K. Rock bands, I think.
（泉）確かＵＫのロックとか
聴くんだよね 斎藤さんって
U.K.?
（コユキ）ＵＫ？
えーと… イギリスのロック
English rock bands.
Like the Beatles and stuff.
ビートルズとか フーとかかな
The Stones are British, too, right?
ストーンズもイギリスだよね？
Yes, the Zeppelin too.
（泉）そう ツェッペリンも
イギリスだよ
（コユキ・泉）エヘッ
（友人）なーんか お邪魔みたい
I feel like I'm in the way.
Huh?
I have an early curfew. Good night!
私 門限早いんで… お先に！
-Is swimming fun?
-Yeah.
（泉）水泳 面白い？
（泉）続きそう？
（コユキ）うん！
-Think you'll continue?
-Yeah.
（泉）そっか よかった
Really? I'm glad.
I was going to stop by
Ryusuke-kun's place.
（コユキ）俺 竜介君とこ
寄ろうと思ってたんだけど…
Maybe I'll join you.
（泉）私も行こうかな…
You have a game on Sunday?
（泉）日曜日に試合？
ああ ミッちゃんに呼ばれたんだ
Yeah, Mit-chan asked me.
（コユキ）あの… グリップが…
（竜介）フッ！
Umm...your grip...
-He just needed a player...
-Ryusuke-kun, your grip...
いや～ 俺は単なる人数集めだから
（コユキ）竜介君 持ち方が…
Huh? You say something, Koyuki?
ん？ コユキ 何か言った？
（泉）コユキ 竜介君に
プレゼントがあるみたいよ
Koyuki has a present for you, Ryusuke-kun.
プレゼント？
A present?
（コユキ）放し飼いだと
野犬狩りに捕まっちゃうから
An unleashed dog may be taken away.
I have been worried
how he doesn't come home lately...
（竜介）ん～ 確かに最近
全然帰ってこなくて—
心配な時とか あるしな
うわっ
（竜介）ちょっと待ってろ
Wait a minute.
（竜介）
うわっ ゴホッ すっげーホコリだぜ
Damn, it's dusty.
フゥ… これ お前にやるよ
You can have this.
（コユキ）うっ え そんな…
No way!
（竜介）お前 最近いろんな音楽
聞いてるみたいだし—
You've been listening
to a lot of music lately.
I figured you might want to play, too.
そろそろ自分でプレーしたくなる
ころかなーと思ってな
年季の入ったギターだね～
It looks quite old.
It's not much, but the sound is good.
（竜介）大したギターじゃねえが
音は ちゃんと出るぞ
Wow!
わあ…
There we go.
（竜介）よーし
（竜介）あ… 切れた
（コユキ）今の… 何ていう曲？
-A string broke.
-What song was that?
（竜介）
ハハ… 適当に弾いただけだよ
-I just played whatever.
-It's the blues, right?
ブルースだよね？
（竜介）ああ
Yeah.
I love the way you play, Ryusuke-kun.
私 竜介君のギター好きだな
（コユキ）俺 もぉ～ めちゃくちゃ
練習して ガンガンやって—
I'm gonna play every waking moment
and get better and better!
バリバリ弾けるよう 頑張ります！
Huh? Yeah.
（カヨ）あー 竜介君！
Oh, Ryusuke-kun!
Mit-chan is steaming mad!
ミッちゃん めっちゃ怒ってるぞ！
（竜介）４時半からじゃなかった？
-Wasn't it at 4:30?
-No, 3:00!
（カヨ）
３時からだよ もう最終回！
It's already the last inning!
４時半って… ん？
I heard 4:30.
Who's that pitcher?
（コユキ）誰？ あのピッチャー
The vocalist for The Crowd,
Manabu Miyazawa.
（竜介）「ザ・クラウド」の
ボーカル 宮沢(みやざわ) 学(まなぶ)
Is he famous?
（コユキ）有名な人？
The Crowd had a huge following
（竜介）クラウドは
すごい数 動員して—
and people thought it was
a matter of time before they debuted.
メジャーデビューも時間の問題と
言われてたバンドなんだ
でも 急にドラムがやめて
バンドも解散
But the drummer suddenly quit
and the band broke up.
The end was really pitiful.
最後はホント あっけなかったな
（バッター）うわぁっ
（バッター）てめえ
どこ投げてんだよ こら！
-Hey! Where're you throwing?!
-Oops! That's weird!
（学）あっれー おかしいな
バットに当たんねえ
I can't hit the bat!
バッター！
あんま動かないでくれる？
Batter! Don't move too much!
-Strike!
-He doesn't seem so great...
（審判）ストライク！
（コユキ）そんなに すごい人には
見えないけど…
If he joins my band,
Taira-kun will join, too.
彼が俺のバンドに入ってくれたら
たぶん平君も入ってくれる
Ryusuke-kun...Look at the other bench.
（カヨ）
竜介君 向こうのベンチ見て
（竜介）栄二…
Eiji...
（カヨ）彼 シリアル・ママの時から
学君のこと誘ってたらしいよ
He's been asking Manabu-kun
to join since the Serial Mama stuff.
（ミッちゃん）おい 竜介！
Hey, Ryusuke!
今 何時だと思ってやがる
（竜介）ごめん！ 時間 間違えた
-Do you know what time it is?!
-Sorry, I had the wrong time.
I told you we had just enough players.
（ミッちゃん）
人数ギリギリだって言ったろ
（竜介）ごめん…
Sorry.
'Cuz of you, I had to call the
one person in the world I didn't wanna.
（ミッちゃん）お前のせいで—
世界で一番 呼びたくない男を
呼んでしまった
Not...Chiba?
（竜介）まさか—
千葉(ちば)？
竜介君？
Ryusuke-kun?
あいつには
３万 借りがあるんだ
-I owe him 30,000 yen.
-Hey! Where's my money?!
（千葉）
あーっ！ てめえ 金返せ！
（竜介）確か 日本には
“出世払い”って言葉がよー
"Pay when you can."
Don't they have that in Japan?
Shut up! You ingrate!
（千葉）
バカぬかせ！ この恩知らずが～！
Chiba! We only have the field
'til 5:00! Hurry it up!
（審判）千葉！
ここ５時までなんだ 早くしろ！
（千葉）けっ！ 覚えてろよ 竜介
Just you wait, Ryusuke.
（学）よしっ
Awright!
（千葉）おわっ
（審判）ボール！
Ball!
（竜介）俺は 正直 学みたいな
ボーカルは好みじゃない
Frankly, I don't care for Manabu's vocals.
But in order to get Taira-kun,
I have no choice.
でも 平君
わりとメジャー志向だからな
-Then what about Chiba?
-Huh? I've never heard him sing.
（カヨ）じゃあ 千葉は？
（竜介）えっ？
あいつの歌なんか聞いたことねーな
千葉には華があるよ
オーラじゃ 学君より上じゃない？
Chiba has charisma. He has
more aura than Manabu-kun.
Oww!
（千葉）いってぇ～っ！
えーっ
今のは よけてくれないとぉ～
You should've moved!
Dammit! I'll kill you!
貴様… 殺す！
Oh, c'mon, don't get so uptight.
やだなー 熱くならないでよ
どうせ君たちの負けなんだしさぁ
You're the losers anyway.
Calm down.
（千葉）フフフン…
Don't touch me!
俺の体に 触るなー！
ハハハ… まっ しゃーねぇな
ハハハハ…
Oh well...
Stop...
やめ…
Stop!
やめろ～！
（学）ん… ん？
（選手）うらぁっ！
（泉）コユキ…
Koyuki...
ヒヒッ ハハッ ハァーッ！
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
（千葉）
タバコ屋のカスミちゃんが好きです
I like Kasumi-chan of the tobacco shop.
"Next Episode"
でも… ファミレスの
ランコちゃんも好きです
"Next Episode"
But I also like Ranko-chan
of the family restaurant.
"Next Episode"